O'Ryan Hedrick



I am a workstation and system administrator with over 10 years of professional experience working with a wide variety of systems, both hardware and software. Starting out in help desk roles has prepared me for communicating with non technical end users and taught me the role of technical support in the business. Transitioning to onsite support brought me into contact with a broad range of hardware and gave me experience from the contractor's side of the IT support industry. Four years working for the US Army as a civilian has broadened my organization/teamwork experience, given me an opportunity to manage systems at a scale well beyond that found in a typical office, and required I come up with new solutions in keeping with numerous policies and regulations. I hope to continue on to a role where I can manage diverse systems and make greater use of the automation skills I've developed over the course of my career.

Evporionco	
Experience	

Sr. System Administrator Edgewater Federal Solutions

September 2022 - November 2023 Albuquerque, NM 40hrs/week - full time

- Document IT related processes and procedures.
- Resolve end-user hardware and software issues.
- Build and deploy kiosk images for HP thin clients using HP Device Manager.
- Coordinate with SCCM admins to create and update packages for Software Center.
- Coordinate with directory admins to update Group Policy for a medical clinic.
- Test new software on medical clinic workstations.
- Research and test automation technology for its use in a medical clinic.
- Handle software/hardware authorization questions and requests for a medical clinic.

IT Specialist II GS-11 Department of Defense - Department of the Army

September 2018 - September 2022 Fort Leonard Wood, MO 40hrs/week - full time

- Configured workstations according to Department of Defense regulations and customer needs
- Managed workstations remotely through SCCM, RDP, and PowerShell
- Remediated issues and vulnerabilities of printers and Windows workstations
- Created and deployed application packages and task sequences using SCCM
- Kept detailed troubleshooting and resolution notes in ITSM/Remedy
- Maintained security clearance and required certifications
- Collected data and coordinated with infrastructure teams to fix issues
- Documented lessons learned to disseminate techniques and configurations amongst the team
- Migrated personal and team documentation to the Microsoft Cloud
- Migrated team processes to PowerApps, including the printer database and a tracker for mandatory training
- Maintained a database tracking printers on post using MS Access, SharePoint, and PowerShell to gather and report data
- Renamed thousands of workstations remotely and after-hours using Powershell

Field Service Technician Decision One

April 2013 - July 2018 St. Louis, MO and Kansas City, MO 2-40hrs/week - part time

- Supported office, library, data center and manufacturing settings
- Resolved hardware issues on workstations and RFID security gates, performing repairs and ordering parts when needed
- Resolved Windows and Microsoft Office issues, install software
- Migrated user data to new machines and verified functionality such as web access, vpn access, etc.
- Installed/deinstalled rack-mounted servers in an enterprise data center
- Documented issues using Remedy, Service Now, or Astea

Technician Super Technology Solutions / Cigna

February 2013 - April 2013 St. Louis, MO 40 hrs/week - full time

- Supported phone and data network connectivity
- Used toner and probe to follow wiring to punchdown block, and punchdown tool to relocate connections

Support Analyst Apex Systems Inc / Enterprise Holdings

August 2010 - November 2012

St. Louis, MO

40hrs/week - full time

- Supported end users via phone and remote system access
- Resolved hardware issues involving thin clients, desktops, laptops, and a variety of peripherals
- Resolved issues involving network access, software, AS/400 print queues, and AS/400 terminal access
- Documented issues in HP Openview, Remedy, and Service Now

Sys	tem Proficiency ————
• SQL queries Pr	Expert • Active Directory Group Policy Expert • Microsoft Excel formula writing Expert • F scripting Expert • Power BI reporting Oficient • Power Apps developement Oficient • Linux command line Oficient • Salt Stack Basic • Git Basic
	Certifications ———
CompTIA Security+CompTIA A+	Army CES Intermediate Leadership
	Other Skills ———
 Creating customized installation media using MDT Creating VMs in ESXi Creating VMs and LXC containers in ProxMox Typesetting with LETEX 	 Simple programming with dotnet and C# Simple programming with TypeScript BAI RMF training
	Education ———
Rankin Technical College St. Louis, MO — Associate of Technology	August 2008 - May 2010
Southwestern Illinois Community College Belleville, IL — Associate of Science	August 2003 - May 2006
	References ———
 Antonio Rodriguez Joshua C Ray Cabriel A Arrizaga 	arodri@sandia.gov Joshberg65@hotmail.com

Gabriel A Areizaga

gabriel.areizaga@gmail.com